(Raj:)and a teeny, tiny
Dark Knight.
(Sheldon:)Obviously, we're no longer
a Justice League.
(Sheldon:)We have no choice but to switch
to our Muppet Baby costumes.
(Raj:)Ooh, I call Kermit.
(Sheldon:)I'm Kermit.
You're Scooter.
(Raj:)Oh, man.
Scooter sucks.
(Raj:)He's the Aquaman
of the Muppet Babies.
(Howard:)No, we can still
make this work.
(Scene:)Leonard,
you talk to Penny.
(Leonard:)What makes you think
I can convince her?
(Howard:)You got her
to have sex with you.
(Howard:)Obviously, your superpower
is brainwashing.
(Leonard:)Okay, let me see
if I understand this.
(Leonard:)You want me
to convince my ex-girlfriend
(Leonard:)to go to a costume party
with her new boyfriend
(Leonard:)just so we can win
a stupid prize?
(Sheldon:)Yes. And make her wear
the black wig. Good luck.
(Penny:)Go away, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)It's Leonard.
(Leonard:)Oh.